

Alejandro Yunes Front-end Dev.

https://vanguardia.tech/alejandro

I am a passionate front-end developer with 5 years of professional experience, specializing in crafting web applications from the initial planning phase to the final deployment using React and its ecosystem. Throughout my career in web development, I have gained knowledge in JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Node, Express, GraphQL, MongoDB, and scrum methodology.

Professional CV

Experience

Aug-present

https://vanguardia.tech

Full Stack Developer

Developed and styled interative Single Page Application (SPA) including the UI and UX with React, Next.js, MongoDB, Express.js, and incorporating both Restful APIs and GraphQL to improve the user experience with this robust and modern tech stack.

June - Aug 2023 Front End Developer

Developed and styled interactive web components delivering high-quality code.

2020 - 2023

Inxeption

Front End Developer

Worked with the UI team to engineer and improve major features of Inxeption ledger.

2019 - 2020

Inaltect S.A.S.

Software Analyst

Developed and maintained mobile Bancolombia features.

2018 - 2019

Freelancer

Full Stack Developer

Development of SPA with NextJS, MongoDB, ExpressJS, Restful Api. Portfolio links in linked in profile.

2014 - 2018

GHR South America S.AS.

Systems Engineer

Support T-Systems internal app, and system admin.

2012 - 2013

Oralaser Clínica las Vegas

Systems Engineer

Management, monitoring installed IT systems infrastructure. LAN Admin: HP ProLiant G5, G6 Win Server 2008R2 – DC, AD, DNS, DHCP, security policies, antivirus console, wireless end user support. And early stages of the website.

Education

2010

Dutchess Community College

Information Management

Associates in Computer Science

2007

Beacon High School

Contact

- https://github.com/alejandroyunes
- https://stackoverflow.com/users/8133300/alejandro-yunes
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/alejandro-yunes-bb562720a/